♪ In the not too
distant future ♪
♪ Way down in Deep 13 ♪
♪ Dr. Forrester and TV's Frank ♪
♪ Were hatching an evil scheme ♪
♪ They hired a temp
by the name of Mike ♪
♪ Just a regular Joe
they didn't like ♪
♪ Their experiment
needed a good test case ♪
♪ So they conked
him on the noggin ♪
♪ And they shot him into space ♪
(rocket rumbling)
- [Mike] Get me down!
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can
find, la-la-la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor
his mind, la-la-la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end, la-la-la ♪
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help of
his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot Roll Call ♪
♪ Cambot, Gypsy,
Tom Servo, Crow ♪
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science
facts, la-la-la ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(metal clanging)
(liquid bubbling)
- Sector four clear.
Platform secure for
traveler, proceed.
- (chuckles) Hi, everyone.
Mike Nelson here.
The robots think there's been
some sort of infiltration
on the Satellite o'
Love, and they think
I need round-the-clock
protection.
Personally, I--
- Gun!
(robots shouting)
(grunts)
- Guys, there's no
assassin up here,
and I don't need protection!
Now, where's Gypsy?
- Security risk, Mike.
We had to deal with her.
(robots shouting urgently)
- [Mike] (groaning) Oh, God--
- Stay down!
- Get down, down, down!
- Oh, guys!
(grunts)
We'll be right back.
(robots shouting)
- Foot, foot!
- [Tom] Head!
(robots screaming)
(mellow synth music)
- Well, anyway, I
think it's sweet
that you guys would
take a bullet for me.
- Take a bullet?
- Yeah, from the assassin.
- An assassin?
Oh, my God, are we in danger?
- We could be killed!
(robots whimpering)
(soft drum music)
- Ah, Mikey!
(speaking foreign language)
Say, you know what
TV's Frank and I
have been getting
into lately, hmm?
Voodoo, yes! (chuckles)
It's a safe, economical way
to inflict evil on the world!
- And it's fun, too.
- (giggles) You
may have noticed,
we've already used the Umbilicus
to send you a little voodoo kit.
Two words of advice, enjoy!
(giggles)
- Hmm, well, now it says here
that if you sprinkle this
dust on one of the dolls,
you can imbue it with the spirit
of whoever you
proclaim it to be.
I think we'll lose
the pins, though.
- Yep.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Let's see if we
can't use voodoo
to do something nice for people!
Hey Crow, who would you like
to do somethin' nice for?
- Um, Jimmy Carter!
- Oh, good.
- I've always liked the man,
and I think he got
dumped on too much.
I think he deserves a hug.
- Hurrah, Jimmy Carter.
- Here you go, Mr. Carter.
- Aww.
(chuckles)
- Now you know who
I've always wanted
to do something nice for, huh?
Ron Hodie, (laughing) I went
to high school with him.
Nice guy, but good grooming
not one of his strong points.
He's probably going
into a meeting right now
and his hair's all mussed up.
I'll just smooth
it back for him.
- That's nice.
- There you go, Ron.
- You know, Mike, I'm
just gonna come right out
and say something I've
always wanted to say to you.
I think you should give Cokie
Roberts a scalp massage.
- I think you're right.
- Oh, and "All Things
Considered" is on right now.
Let's check it out.
- Well.
- [Cokie] Thank you, senator.
This is Cokie Roberts,
and you're listening,
oh, oh, oh, that feels good.
Oh, that is just what I need.
Oh, I'm in heaven.
- Maybe that's enough.
(jungle music)
- Well, the whole
voodoo motif continues
with this week's experiment.
It's from the
mid-'80s, and it's,
hey!
(snickering)
It's, hey.
- Ah, perfect.
(all giggling)
- It's called
"Zombie Nightmare,"
and it stars Adam West and...
(jungle drums banging)
(Bots humming)
(alarm blaring)
- Oh, we got movie sign.
(doors clanging)
♪ Do do that voodoo that you ♪
- Look, Lisa Bonet
on any given day.
(Mike chuckles)
- Is that her hope chest?
- [Mike] It's where
she keeps Meatloaf.
(muttering)
- [Tom] Honey, time to get up.
You've got a civics
test this morning.
- [Mike] Oh, no, he's gone over.
- She should pack some more
foam peanuts around him.
(chuckling)
- You know, these guys
come packed like this.
But just try getting 'em
back in the box. (chuckles)
- [Tom] Here, try some chaps.
(mumbling)
Little Shalimar for me.
- Danny Bonaduce on
any given morning.
(coughing)
(lip smacking and groaning)
(shrieking)
- [Mike] Yeah, I know, I know.
("Ace of Spades" by Motorhead)
- Cool.
- [Mike] Oh, this is from
the new Sinatra album.
- Every zombie nightmare I have,
I'm naked at a hockey game.
- [Mike] Do zombies
ever try to analyze
their nightmares, do you think?
- [Tom] Is this the
information superhighway
that I've heard them
talk so much about?
- Oh, goodie!
- [Tom] I don't
think fingerprints
are actually labeled like this.
- And Tia Carrere, we may
have to pay attention.
- [Tom] Nya, nya, nya, nya.
- [Mike] Manuska, oh,
that's my manicurist.
- What a ditz.
Ditz.
- [Mike] Wish I could
understand the lyrics.
- Maybe it's for the
young generation.
They have so much to say.
- Motorhead, I have
their new collection
of Cole Porter tunes.
- Uh, that's woman school.
- [Tom] Oh, I think
Thor is fabulous.
He's just divine.
- [Mike] Oh,
Deathmask, they played
at my parents'
anniversary party.
- [Tom] I saw Fist when
they opened for Badfinger.
♪ The ace of spades ♪
- [Tom] These young
men sound so angry.
- Oh, yes, listen to them.
- [Tom] Young people have a
lot to say through their music.
♪ You know I'm born to lose ♪
- Ah, he's gonna lose.
♪ But that's the
way I like it baby ♪
♪ I don't wanna live forever ♪
- [Tom] Uh, okay, so he's
mad 'cause he's losing,
yet that's the way he likes it.
- Well, then
everything works out.
- [Tom] Oh, Mariners
opening day.
- [Man] All right,
pick it up, pick it up.
- [Mike] Pride of the zombies.
- You know if you got
a zombie on the team
you gotta play him
in right field.
- [Tom] Larry
Mondello as the babe.
- [Man] Go to
second, double play.
Pick it up, pick it up.
- [Mike] Unchain me.
- Here we go, a pop up.
- Oh, my allergies.
I shouldn't be outside.
Oh, hey, I caught it.
- [Kid] Yay, Dad!
That's great!
- [Tom] Jackie Vernon
hitting a little fun goal.
- Third base, little pop up.
- That's the best
hit I ever seen.
- [Mike] Yeah, well,
you're five, okay?
- Zombies look okay this year.
With just a little
pitching work they could...
- [Man] Pitcher,
back to the box.
- [Mike] James Earl
Ray in back there?
- [Tom] Please rain
so I can leave.
- The teenage handicap.
- The hell is she doing here?
- [Mike] The hell
are we doing here?
- [Tom] Hmm, I see
an open back seat.
I think I'll move down there.
- [Man] Okay, third
base, that's yours.
- [Tom] Third base.
- C'mon, let's go have some fun.
- [Mike] Tough skins.
- [Man] All right,
pick it up, pick it up.
- [Mike] Hah, tickle
patrol, hee hee hee.
- Marshall Wallace
in the stands today.
And here's George Wendt,
he's batting two 10.
- Well, hi there.
Who are you?
Sure, I'll take you
home. (chuckles)
- [Mike] Holy cow,
that's a big family.
- [Tom] You know, chunky
guys attract people.
That's a known given fact.
- [Mike] He's husky.
(ominous orchestral music)
- Then the doctor
found Lady Macbeth
wandering in the halls
to assuage her guilt.
- [Mike] Well,
I'm sure strolling
at Howard Beach
won't be a problem.
- [Tom] No, you can't
be a junior T-man.
Oh, a wise guy, eh?
You palooka, why, I oughta.
- [Tom] Nathan, quit hitting me.
- Hey, wanna see some sumac?
- [Tom] The long walk home.
Actually it is.
- [Mike] I think I'll walk
down Certain Doom Lane.
(humming)
- [Batten] This pretty,
young thing has just walked
into the wrong neighborhood.
- I do believe you're
right, Mr. Batten.
- Oh, this would
never happen nowadays.
- You're gonna come
into my neighborhood,
you gotta pay the toll.
- Yeah, relax babe,
you're gonna enjoy this.
- [Girl] Help, somebody help me.
- [Tom] Son, go rescue her.
(screaming)
- Excuse me boys,
what's going on here?
- [Thug] Stay out
of this, old man.
- [Boy] We were only
having some fun, old man,
but if you want
us to cut it out,
then we'll cut you out.
- [Tom] Oh, clever.
(grunting and yelling)
Fight choreography
by Dom Deluise.
(screaming)
- I'll go start dinner.
- [Tom] Boy, she
can nap anywhere.
I'm husky.
- My wig hurts.
- [Woman] Bill, is she okay?
- [Bill] I think so.
- [Mike] This is like
Dicken's view of the suburbs.
(screaming)
- [Tom] Ewww, yuck.
- [Woman] Bill, bill.
- I'm hungry.
- [Woman] Oh dear God in Heaven.
- Get off her you're
gonna kill her.
A young Joe Pepitone
ponders his fate.
- [Tom] Great, I joined
the big brother program
for one day and then
(exasperated groan).
- Eddie Van Halen.
- [Tom] No, it's
Valerie Bertinelli.
♪ She's a small town girl
on a Saturday night ♪
- Dyslexia strikes the
scoreboard industry.
- [Mike] Wait, that's not
dyslexic, Park Harpell,
that's Canadian
English, this is Canada.
- [Tom] Well, whadda ya know?
Everybody move in, come on.
- His hair's bouncin'
and behavin'.
I think he's got
a gland problem.
- [Tom] The Giants
win the pennant,
the Giants win the pennant,
the Giants win the pennant.
- Just let him get to first,
he never gets to first.
His parents are here.
(horrified gasps)
- God.
- [Mike] Jeez.
- [Tom] I don't
want to see that.
- [Mike] That actually
was a nice reveal.
- [Tom] Ever since Dad got
murdered things have been great.
- [Mike] I like the ting
sound, (mock laughing).
Okay, lady, we
need our payments.
- [Teenager] Hey ma, we won.
- That's nice, son.
You forgot the groceries.
- [Tom] I'm too dreamy
to remember groceries.
- Look, sorry Mom.
- [Tom] Mom, get off
the neighbor's porch.
- Take a jacket,
it looks like rain.
- Okay, thanks mom.
I'll be back soon, okay?
- [Tom] And son,
cover the nipples,
the neighbors have
been complaining.
- [Mike] God, he's beautiful.
- Ah, the club Jobless.
- [Mike] Disco's back
and hotter than ever.
- [Tom] God, I never wanted
to see this era again.
- It's a sensible rave.
- [Mike] Office temps cut loose.
- [Tom] I took my real
estate exam yesterday.
- [Mike] Really,
that's so fascinating.
You see what Denise
did at work today?
She jammed up the copier again.
- Steve is such a kiss-up
and I think he's
taking paperclips home.
- [Tom] You know,
Mike, you're right.
This is either America ten
years ago or Canada today.
(laughing)
- [Mike] Ouch.
What is this,
Death Mask featuring
Olivia Newton John?
- [Tom] Oh, look over there,
the Uppy Reader Editorial Board.
- [Mike] Okay, Q of A,
everyone wait for the beat.
If that's Leif
Garret I am leaving.
- [Tom] Me too.
Okay, so then the finance
comes in and he goes, "Hey".
(laughing)
- Excuse me, kids.
Could you keep the noise down?
- [Mike] I'm tryin'
to score here, okay?
- Keep it down, man?
Hey, why don't you find
some place else to sit
while you still can?
- [Tom] Huh?
- You know, Tom, as
your parole officer
I need to caution you about
that sort of behavior.
- [Mike] What, yeah my hair's
frosted, what about it?
Oh, wait come back.
Why do I always lash out?
- [Tom] He kind of looks
like Michelle Pfeifer.
- [Tom] Okay, where was
I, Leather Tuscanaio came
in Patsy and Ralph
Mouth (laughing).
- These young life weekends
are gettin' out of hand.
- Well, whadda we got here.
I didn't know elementary schools
were on vacation this week.
- [Mike] Duh.
- Uh, real tough
guy, any suggestions?
- [Tom] It takes a man to
wear Farrah Fawcett hair.
- Pay the check, man, and
let's get the hell out of here.
- [Mike] See, he's
got a vulnerable side.
- [Bouncer] Okay now, you
all come back here real soon
when you're over 21.
- Man, I wouldn't come back
to this hole if I was 41.
- What a brilliant bowl mole.
- [Tom] Very witty.
- [Mike] Mentos,
the Fresh Maker.
(laughing)
- There she is, it's
Tia, Tia, Tia, whoa.
(upbeat music)
- Cut it, okay.
(Tom blabbering melodically)
♪ St Elmo's Fire ♪
- [Mike] Don't.
(teens chattering loudly)
Do you think this speaks
for a whole generation,
like "Reality Bites"?
- Yeah, "Big Chill."
- What would you know
about parents, inbreed?
- I know your mother!
- [Jim] Oh, you
know my mother, eh?
- I feel so left out.
- [Bob] Okay, okay, cut
it out right now, hey.
- [Mike] Can't see anything!
- The night is young,
and so are we.
(giggles)
So let's get totally
tanked up, go down
to the dance at Lincoln.
Then we'll pick up
some sleazy chicks.
- [Mike] Aim high.
- [Woman] Thanks a lot, pinhead.
- [Man] I meant them, baby.
I've got my sleazy chick.
- [Mike] He always
knows just what to say.
Charmer.
You know, this is
how my folks met.
(laughing)
(upbeat rock music)
- Let's go to Perkins, woo!
- [Mike] Oh, they're
shining, sleazy chicks.
- [Tom] You're listening
to the Light FM.
And now, here's FIST.
♪ Life your voices up ♪
- [Mike] Lick your voices?
- Oh, it's really loud in back.
♪ No stopping ♪
(imitating vocals)
- [Mike] Well,
let's just go home.
- [Tom] I don't know,
usually this neighborhood
is crawling with sleazy chicks.
(screaming)
- Oh, why must they scream so?
- [Mike] Oh, that's rage, honey.
♪ While the clown
knows you're here ♪
- [Mike] There you go, Joe
Weider's protein blast.
- Have you got the provolone?
- Hey, Tony, would I forget
how much your mama
like provolone.
- [Tom] Big 7-Eleven
item, provolone.
- How is the new
job working out?
- It's not bad, sir.
Except they want
me to cut my hair.
- [Tom] And they
want you to bathe.
- Don't.
You cut the hair, you
lose the strike, no?
- [Mike] Just pack
the groceries, pop.
- Anything else?
- [Tom] Oh, some body oil.
- Wait, I forgot my wheat germ.
- Ah.
Right in the back on the left.
- [Tom] Next to the
dessicated liver pills.
(light synth music)
- [Mike] Synthesizer
signals suspense.
- [Tom] Oh, looks like
a run on wheat germ.
(imitating synth)
- Oh, God, did you see
where he pulled it from?
- [Tom] Oh, no.
- [Mike] I'm the NRA.
- [Tom] All right, hand
over the Toblerone.
- What do you want, boys?
- [Mike] Ew, it's stuck
in his hinder-holster.
- [Tom] Do you accept these?
- All your money, sucker!
- Mama mia.
(sniffing)
- What has that been?
- [Mike] Are you
hiring right now?
- What's that?
Go check it out.
- [Mike] You want to try
a sample of Tony's pizza?
Oh, let's see, night crawlers,
leeches, sucker minnows,
bobbers on sale!
Hey!
(yelps)
- Phil!
Phil, what the hell is
going on back there!
- [Mike] Courtesy
boy on two, please.
- Phil!
- [Tom] And three and
four and jazz hands, pop!
(grunting)
- [Tom] Watch it.
- I don't understand retail.
Oh!
- [Mike] Oh, nice
use of his area.
- Can you get the door for me.
Thanks.
- [Mike] I'm going to show
the world your butt crack!
- [Tom] Ew.
- Get back to the
sewer, dirt bag.
(Tarzan yelling)
- [Tom] Hey, what's
going on, guys?
Oh!
- And you too!
Get out of here!
- [Mike] Bow down to my nipples.
Oh, great.
Now they're closed.
- [Tom] Oh, dear God.
Well, paper or plastic?
- [Mike] Hey, how come
there's no pictures
of Italians on the wall?
- You're a good boy, Tony.
Your papa would be proud of you.
- But you need to pay your tab.
- What do I owe you?
(laughing)
- Give my best to
your mama, huh?
- [Tom] And take
an air freshener.
- Grazie.
Grazie, Tony.
Grazie.
- [Mike] Yeah, Prego, whatever.
- It would be fun to
open a convenience
store, what the
hell was I thinking?
(chuckling)
♪ They say the neon lights
are bright on Winnipeg ♪
- [Mike] They're missing
the forest for the trees
in this whole
sleazy chick thing.
(suspenseful music)
- Oh, I forgot tampons.
Well, I'm probably
okay for tonight.
- [Mike] Ah, an actor
conveys chilliness.
(upbeat rock music)
- [Tom] You know, maybe
they should pay attention
to the message of the song.
- Bodybuilder by day,
Trappist monk by night.
- [Tom] Oh, guys, I just
realized, he put the groceries
in with his jock strap.
- [Mike] Ew.
(gagging)
- Searching three provinces
for sleazy chicks.
I had no idea Canada
was this much fun!
- [Tom] Uh-oh.
Don't worry, his area
will protect him.
(car thudding)
(tires screeching)
Oh, maybe not.
- Wow.
(all shouting)
- [Tom] I think we hit a moose.
- Come on, turn the tape over!
(hums)
- [Tom] When bad things
happen to beefy guys.
- [Mike] Hey, Tony,
I'm being robbed again.
Could you, oh.
There's a dead hunk in
the middle of the road.
Dead boy.
- Tony, who could have
done this terrible thing.
Please, please help me.
- [Tom] Hi.
I'm a Samaritan.
can I do anything?
- Tony.
Oh.
- Geez, it's Tony!
- [Mike] Why, I'd know
that batch anywhere.
- I think he is--
- What happened?
What happened, Mr. Peters?
- [Tom] Peters?
- [Mike] Hank Peters,
Italian grocer.
(suspenseful music)
(coughs)
♪ When your car hits a guy
and his body goes fly ♪
♪ That's a dead guy ♪
- [Louise] My boy!
- [Mike] Tonight, on
"Double-Wide Hospital."
- [Louise] My boy!
- That's the Canadian
health care system.
Bush warned us about this.
- I'm sorry, Louise.
It happened so fast, I
never see who did it.
- [Tom] So, you want
him in the garage?
(cries)
- [Mike] If you hadn't
sent him for groceries,
he'd be alive.
Well, anyway.
- There's nothing we
can do for him now.
Let me call for the police.
- Oh, he never paid
for the provolone.
- No.
- [Tom] Wow.
- They aren't going
to get away this.
They're not going to
do it to me again.
- [Tom] Housewife vigilante.
- They're not going to take
my son and get away with it.
- But Louise--
- Quiet, Hank!
- Geez, her son dies,
she gets really bossy.
- [Tom] Wow.
- Do you know Molly Mokembe?
- [Mike] Sure, she
did my color chart.
- Not really, ma'am.
- Louise what do you want
with that crazy Haitian.
- Never mind, Hank.
Earl, run over to
Molly Mokembe's house.
Bring her back here right away.
- Sure, Mrs. Washington.
Come with me, Jimmy.
- Yeah, sure.
- [Mike] Okay if we
stop at the roadhouse
for a couple of
brewtowskis first?
- Anybody think about
resuscitating Tony, or not, or--
- [Tom] Reverse!
Put it in reverse!
Phew.
- What do you want from
that crazy old bat?
Hmm?
- A favor.
She owes me one.
- [Mike] That's an
odd nativity scene.
(light acoustic guitar music)
♪ All the leaves are brown ♪
♪ The leaves are brown ♪
♪ And the skies are gray ♪
(humming)
- [Mike] Okay, so who's
going to carpool tomorrow?
- [Tom] It's just
like a separate piece,
except they didn't leave
a dead guy in the street.
- Well, I mean, like, who cares.
He was just another one of them.
- Right.
Screw him.
He's not talking
anyway, so, uh, who's
going to come
looking for us, huh?
(knocking)
- Hey, we're doing
a scene out here.
- Are you okay?
What's the matter?
- [Mike] This Kansas song
just makes me so sad.
- Feeling bad, huh?
- [Tom] Need a hug?
♪ I've been ignored in
a world of darkness ♪
- No.
No, man.
I kind of liked it.
- [Mike] He always finds the
bright side of everything.
- You know, just taking
his life like that.
Snuffing out that big candle.
- [Tom] Oh, he's
waxing philosophical.
- Splat.
- [Mike] He needs a teen center.
- [Tom] Yeah.
- He didn't look so tall when
I got through with him, man.
Christ.
It was so easy.
- [Tom] Well, neat.
- [Mike] They must've been.
- And there's nothing
he can do about it.
- [Crow] Well, he could
become a zombie and haunt
you the rest of your life.
- I want to go home.
(doors clanking)
- Gah!
(coughs)
(groans)
(yelps)
- Huh.
Could have sworn
I hit something.
Oh well.
(upbeat synth music)
(light orchestral music)
♪ Is this the little
boy I carried ♪
- [Mike] Anyway, I should mosey
back to the grocery store.
- Good thing she got a
full size picnic table.
- [Tom] Tina Turner
brought some hot dish.
- Molly.
- [Mike] My son's dead.
What's new with you.
- [Louise] Molly,
it's been too long.
- [Mike] She's a freak out.
- My son.
- Andrea Martin is in mourning.
- I know.
I know.
- I never do anything
nice and easy.
♪ Left a good job in the city ♪
- Louise, what is this?
- I'm trying to work
here, excuse me.
- Quiet, un-believer.
- [Tom] I'm not an
unbeliever, I'm an agnostic.
- She knows that old Molly
Mokembe can give her--
- [Mike] Use your words.
- What you police can not.
- She must be from Newfoundland.
- Vengeance for her son's death.
- [Tom] What about Van Johnson?
Did you catch that?
- [Molly] Now.
- [Mike] Hey, hoser, take off.
- Me?
- [Molly] Yes, you.
You go to Mr. Cabretti's house.
- Is she half she-e-ep?
- [Molly] Tell him I need
blood from a live animal.
- [Tom] And the lime
and the coconut.
- Am I over-doing this?
- Hurry.
- Zombie interns.
- Before the sun is up.
- [Tom] TomTom Makuts?
- Mr. Hurley.
- [Mike] Mr. Peters, Mr. Hurley.
Mr. Hurley, Mr. Peters.
- Tonight I will need your help.
- [Tom] I am moving
my sofa, and--
- And what you see and
hear you must never
tell any living soul.
Not that, that they
would ever believe you.
- [Mike] , You know, come
to think of it, Molly,
we'll just go for a
traditional funeral.
(percussive music)
- They called Sly Stone.
- [Tom] No, it's Rasta,
the kooky dread clown.
- You must understand what I do.
- [Mike] I don't work
weekends, and I only
create zombies during
business hours.
- I cannot bring life
back to your boy.
- [Mike] Not for the kind of
prices we're talking about.
- I can--
- [Tom] Give you a
coupon for next time.
And may God bless.
Good night.
- Hold him in this plain--
- [Mike] Sure, fine, whatever.
- Until his death
has been avenged.
- How will he know?
- [Molly] He will be in a
state between life and death.
- There may be some discharge.
- And the image of his killers--
- [Mike] The age of Aquarius.
- The last fleeting second
before the end of his life--
- [Mike] Right, right.
- Is burned--
- [Tom] She's got pretty eyes.
- [Mike] What the.
- Into his soul like a brand.
- And this is going
to run me, uh, what?
- [Mike] Got a chill there.
- He knows who has
done this to him.
- [Tom] Yeah, man.
Para-sail, jet-ski,
best in the island.
- And tonight we
will have revenge.
Now stand back.
- [Tom] For Dutch masters!
Think it's going to rain?
- Be not an exact science.
- [Mike] Oh she's back-pedaling.
- We take the blood
of this animal
and the hair of this boy.
- Wow, look at all the candles.
What'd they do, loot a Pier 1?
- [Tom] Well, this so much
better than the intensive care
unit at the hospital.
- [Mike] Yeah,
what could they do?
Whoa, a short!
Sorry.
- The steady hand
of the wunderworld--
- [Mike] You wascally wabbit.
- Who will come this
night to take your soul
to a dark place.
- [Tom] By the way, Tony
wasn't a donor, was he, mon?
- Rise again, young warrior--
- [Mike] Boy, ever since
Vatican II they've really--
- And feel again the warmth--
- I don't want to
feel again the worm!
- And light.
To a bright place.
- [Tom] I just have a much
different image of Canada.
- Rise.
- [Mike] Now, look,
maybe this kind of stuff
goes over in Vegas.
- And avenge thyself!
- I've just got to pee.
- [Tom] What stage
of grieving is this?
- [Mike] It's the goofy stage.
- [Tom] I guess so.
(percussive music)
- [Mike] Voodoo stuff
here, voodoo stuff there.
Throw in a little Crystal Lite.
(chants)
She's so good she doesn't
follow any recipes.
A pinch here, a pinch there,
he's a zombie, who cares?
- [Tom] Oh, hope the
lawn's not too dry.
- Ace Frehley has this
same kind of business now.
- [Tom] Does he?
- [Mike] Hello?
What am I, alone in here?
People, this is voodoo!
- [Tom] In the words of
David Steinberg, booga booga.
- The master voodoo,
master of the age.
- [Mike] Oh, she's
probably Missouri Senate.
They're really
hardcore like this.
- Whew.
- [Tom] Hey, I'm in here.
(speaking foreign language)
- So, does Molly care this
crate around with her?
Or does that, how does
that, I don't get it.
- [Mike] Watch, next to the
power goes out, no candles.
- [Tom] Ooh, and then come
baaaack to the, this guy's dead,
what the hell?
(speaking foreign language)
Okay, now I'm going
to need a volunteer
from the audience, mon.
- [Mike] And you are
completely dead, sir,
am I right about that?
(speaking foreign language)
- [Tom] I'm in
over my head here.
- Eh, what you've got
here is a dead man.
So I'm going to have to take
him into the shop overnight.
Didn't know the main
rod was thrown either.
- [Mike] She's
resurrecting Neil Young.
(speaking foreign language)
- [Tom] Holy buckets,
it's working!
- [Mike] I was supposed to get
milk, wheat germ, what else?
(speaking foreign language)
(roars)
- [Tom] Why you wake
me up so early, Ma?
(gasps)
- [Mike] There it is.
Thank you.
- [Tom] Maybe this
wasn't such a good idea.
(roars)
- [Mike] The early
morning call to voodoo.
(yawns)
- [Mike] Oh, so the zombie
settled down, got himself a job.
- [Tom] What's up?
Way to put the fridge
in the hallway, Ma.
- Well, good morning to you.
- Mom, I just killed a guy.
Give me a break.
- And, uh, just what time
did you get in last night?
As if I didn't know from
the racket that you made.
And where's your father's car?
Or did you wreck that one, too?
- [Mike] The Anne
Mira of Canada.
- Huh?
You know, just because
your father's company
leases the damn
things doesn't mean
that you can go driving
them in to telephone poles.
Are you deaf, or just dumb?
- [Tom] Hmm?
Hmm.
- You are disgusting.
You're not going to get
to your next birthday
if you don't get
your act together.
- Up yours.
- What did you say,
you disrespectful punk?
(screams)
- [Mike] Oh, didn't stick.
Must not be done.
- [Tom] Ah, the drama
of the gifted child.
- Oh, and, mom, have a nice day.
(heavy rock music)
- [Mike] I should
have him killed.
- [Tom] They live at
Marcus Welby's house?
- Oh darn, I left
the car radio on.
- [Tom] First you kill
a guy, then you're
throwing pasta a your mom.
What next?
- [Mike] Where does it end?
Need to go buy some
more vermicelli.
- Wow, he's a rebel.
Look at him cross
that center line.
- [Mike] The ghetto of
Pleasant Valley Acres.
♪ Let's go ♪
- [Tom] Okay, well,
let's go then.
- [Mike] Okay.
- It's "The Kids in the Hall."
♪ Speeding down the motorway ♪
- [Tom] Welcome to
Landfill Junction.
♪ 1000 miles another day ♪
♪ I'm not sure when I'll ride ♪
- [Mike] Let's follow our hero
as he heads down
to Payless Shoes.
♪ Living for today ♪
- [Tom] Yeah.
♪ Come on, let's go ♪
- [Tom] Hey.
You're number one there, man.
♪ Come on let's go ♪
- [Tom] Well, come on, let's go.
- Yeah, I guess they want
us to go, so let's go.
♪ Let's go ♪
- [Crow] I'd go if you'd
stop singing already.
- [Tom] I, I, I think
we're not supposed to go.
- [Mike] Oh.
- [Tom] It says let's go.
Oh, no, I guess not.
(upbeat synth music)
♪ And you're screaming
red hot rage ♪
♪ I don't know if ♪
- So, apparently the director
of photography went for a drive.
- [Mike] Say what you will,
he's a cautious driver
who maintains an
adequate space cushion.
- [Tom] Oh, and he
drives defensively
and at a moderate speed.
♪ And you know we never lose ♪
- [Tom] Woo!
♪ Come on let's go ♪
- Not the Twist and Cream!
- [Mike] That's creme.
- [Tom] Oh.
- [Mike] Creme, not creme.
- The plot is furthered
by a good parking space.
- [Mike] It's Tommy Stinson.
- [Tom] Yeah, only heavier.
- Good morning, killers.
- Threw spaghetti
at my mom today.
- Keep it down, you jerk.
- Hey, where's your dad's car?
- Well, it, uh, it
seems I picked up
a little front-end
damage somewhere.
So I, uh, dropped it off
in my cousin's garage.
- [Tom] Hey, they're opening
a new Twist and Creme.
- Guys, I think we lucked out.
- Nothing in the papers?
- Not a word in the papers.
Or on the radio.
Nothing about our little
nocturnal adventure.
- [All] Ew.
- Maybe he's not dead.
Maybe he just went
home or something.
- Are you kidding?
When Jimbo wastes
them, they stay wasted.
- [Mike] Hey, that's
a good slogan.
- Yeah, Jim's right,
deranged but right.
- He's the funny one.
- Yeah, that guy didn't
do any walking last night.
- Hey, Jim, uh, was wondering,
where are your dad's wheels?
- As I was telling
rocket brain here,
I ditched the death
mobile a my cousin's.
- [Mike] Excuse me, I have to
become even more unappealing.
- Well, I'd love to, uh,
sit and chat with
the brain trust here,
but I think I'll order myself
some breasts and thighs.
- [Mike] Ugh.
- So why is he the leader?
- [Mike] I don't think, eh.
- What an ass.
- [Tom] This one, prototype
for Richard Carpenter.
- Well, at least he
got rid of the car.
The last thing we
need is attention.
- Jesus.
- I could think of
something we need now.
- [Tom] A hot fudge
brownie delight.
- Hey, this is my wrist.
- Oh, damn, I need to
get to the academy.
Mrs. Goldstein's coming
in at three o'clock.
Are you coming?
- [Mike] Academy
- Not quite, but
the day is young.
- [Tom] I think that
was a single entendre.
- Excuse me.
- Come on, Mags,
I promise, you've
never seen anything like it.
- [Mike] It's a
stamp from Indonesia!
- Look, Jim, I
prefer men with ones
that can be seen without the
aid of an electron microscope.
- [Tom] Ones?
- Thinking.
Thinking.
- That's all right, baby.
I'll make you beg for it.
- [Tom] Wow, got her back
with that one, mister.
Wow.
- [Mike] Oh, Garrison
Keillor laughing.
- What?
What?
(light synth music)
♪ In cars ♪
- Wow, Mrs. Goldstein.
(whistles)
- [Tom] Is she playing
tennis with Kraftwerk?
- Live the active lifestyle.
- [Mike] Not so hard.
Oh, now, now my shoelaces.
Do you have my
puffer, because I--
I'm just going to let you win.
Sucked.
- [Tom] But why now?
I'm having hard enough time.
- She's got 30 pounds on him.
- [Tom] Yes, go
swimming, play tennis,
enjoy the active lifestyle
in your new hair.
- ESPN at three a.m.
- [Mike] Taste me steel, please.
- [Tom] Yeah, pretty much.
Yeah, that's me.
- Did we accidentally
switch to a different movie?
- I, I...
So, how does this
further the plot?
- [Mike] How does this
further the game of tennis,
for that matter?
- Oh, Mrs. Tennis Lady,
don't take off the thing.
- [Mike] Wow.
- Oh, no, don't, lady.
- [Tom] Yes, not since the
eating scene in "Tom Jones"
has a movie been so
rife with sensuality.
- And the score is love-love.
- [Mike] Ladies and
gentlemen, Frederick Douglass.
- Is that you, Pete?
- [Pete] Yeah.
Yeah, it's me, Joe.
I'll lock up.
- Okay, man.
See you tomorrow.
- Basically I'll lock up
the town's largest tennis--
- [Tom] So many
women tennis players
wish they were that guy.
- [Mike] A voodoo ceremony
for that guy's backhand.
(chuckling)
- Here's to your new life.
Mazel tov.
- [Tom] This one makes me laugh.
Ha ha.
- [Mike] Oh, God,
I love candles.
- That one, he's not
afraid of silence.
- [Tom] Nope, doesn't always
have to be talking, you know.
- [Mike] Mm-mm.
(sniffs)
Yuck.
(metal clanging)
- [Mike] Ah!
Meanwhile at Anoka
Ramsey Technical College.
- Must register for semester.
- [Tom] The dead zone is for
loading and unloading only.
(metal clanging)
- Wow, stop it.
- [Mike] You know, if
you're a zombie, you really
don't want to
over-schedule, because you
can't move that fast.
Because you're a zombie.
- Yeah.
- [Tom] Hmm.
I see.
(metal pinging)
- [Tom] Oh, dammit.
Radiator.
- Wow, John Cage
on the soundtrack.
- [Tom] Oh, criminy,
they're closed.
(light synth music)
Hmm?
- [Mike] Oh, no.
No.
- [Tom] Oh, boy.
- [Mike] Oh, he put on a skort.
- [Tom] I beg you
to think this over.
- Turn back.
- [Mike] No.
It's not too late.
- [Tom] Oh.
No, no, no, no.
- No.
- He's wearing jockey for her!
Ah!
- [Tom] You're supposed
to shower first!
- Or at least rinse
out your jockeys.
Ew.
- [Mike] Ew.
- [Tom] Fungus and thing.
- Oh, and he's sucking
up bathtub water!
Oh!
(metal scraping)
- I know my locker's around
here somewhere, now where?
Is it that one?
(light synth music)
- [Mike] Enya.
Sorry, got a cramp.
I can't get up.
- Can we turn on the
fuzzy bubbles, please?
- [Tom] God, he's touching me.
I specifically have no-touch
clause in my contract.
(laughs)
(metal clanging)
- What was that?
- What was what?
- I thought I heard
something in the locker room.
- Oh, come on.
There's nobody here.
It's probably just old Joe
trying to sneak a peek of you.
He's a horny old guy.
- Oh, please, just
for me, just go see.
I swear to God I
heard something.
- There's nobody else here.
The place is locked up.
- Please.
- [Tom] Hey, she's got
her hair on sideways.
- There was a noise,
I'm telling please go.
- All right.
(wretches)
- [Mike] Oh, he just had
to get that in, didn't he.
- [Tom] No, no, no!
- [Mike] No!
(shouting)
- [Tom] Hate that.
- See, look, I told you,
there's nobody here.
(roars)
(screams)
- [Tom] Oh, zombie chiropractor.
Oh, thank you.
- [Mike] Pool cleaner, ma'am.
pH check and I'll
be out of your way.
(water splashing)
There goes a great
tennis player.
(growls)
- [Tom] Wedgie!
(screams)
- [Mike] Oh, excuse me, but
the dead don't tread water.
- [Tom] George Romero's
"Casey at the Bat."
(screams)
- She must have studied
under Jamie Lee Curtis.
(screams)
- [Mike] Eh, hang on.
Oh, my ankle.
Ow.
(screams)
- [Tom] "Grady,"
this fall on NBC.
- Hey, Fred.
- Look at that.
- [Tom] She's briskly
jogging from him.
- [Mike] You know, he did
kill that creep for her.
She could thank him, at least.
- [Tom] Hey, it's your
typical free week at the Y.
- Hey, come on back and
shag some flies for me.
- [Mike] Don't use the exit.
- Come on, we need a
short center fielder.
- [Tom] Oh, zombie
never could hit a curve.
- [Mike] You know, John
Goodman on Hume Cronin's back
could outrun this guy.
- Oh, no, her bra strap broke.
- [Tom] What next?
(screams)
- Okay, okay, I'm
giving you a head start.
♪ Woke up, fell out of bed ♪
♪ Dragged the comb
across my head ♪
♪ Found my way down the stairs ♪
- [Crow] What's going to happen?
I, oh.
(upbeat synth music)
♪ Touchdown in the land
of the Delta blues ♪
♪ In the middle of
the pouring rain ♪
- Oh, wonderful.
- Yeah.
- Hey, thanks for that back rub.
Water feels great.
- Yeah, hardly
feel those injuries
I sustained when
you ran me over.
(laughs)
- Let me just say, I
am totally relaxed.
(giggles)
- Servo, stop that!
- What?
What, Crow?
What?
Huh?
- Stop it, you nutty nut nut.
- Crow, I'm not doing anything.
(screaming)
(spitting)
- Hey, guys.
(screaming)
- Dinner?
(alarm blaring)
- [Tom] Where'd
you get the fish?
- [Mike] Hey, Conan O'Brien.
(camera shutter clicking)
- [All] We didn't do it.
- Another unruly crowd.
- [Man] Frank.
- Yeah?
- Forensic's just
about finished.
The ME wants to see you inside.
- [Mike] What did I do?
- Great.
- [Tom] Fine,
everybody dump on me.
- Look, uh, keep an eye on
my star witness here, okay?
- Say, officer, can I go now?
- [Frank] Uh, soon.
I've got a few more questions.
- Can I have a Tahitian treat?
- [Tom] Poor guy.
Hmm.
- [Mike] Yep, yep, this
is the scene they always
show on "That's Hollywood,"
with Tom Bosley.
- [Tom] Beautiful.
Beautiful.
- [Mike] That's Bosley.
(camera shutter clicking)
- Now let's get one
of you with the body.
- Wishful thinking, doc?
- Ah, Frank.
Nice to see you could
make it to the clambake.
- [Tom] Are you
talking to the Penguin?
- Oh, what the hell Else?
would I be doing at three
o'clock in the morning?
- I don't want to know.
- See your boys in white
are moving right along.
- Well, you've probably
noticed the lovely lady
on her way out.
Now the boys are trying
to fish lover-boy
out of the swimming
pool full of blood.
- [Mike] Uh, about your voice.
- You get anything out
of the good old Joe?
- Oh, old Joe is a wealth
of useful information.
- Yeah?
- Do you know how many times
they refinish the
floors in here?
(laughs)
According to Joe, nobody
came in, no one could get in.
Now, bodies A and B stayed late
for a post-game celebration,
as was their habit.
- Yeah.
- Old Joe was sleeping like
a baby, never heard a thing.
- [Tom] So who put the
12-year-old in charge
of the investigation here?
- So what do you
think, double suicide?
- [Mike] No thanks.
- Oh, sure, sure.
Lover-boy smashes her head
in with the baseball bat,
then snaps his own neck
with his bare hands
and throws himself in
the pool out of remorse.
- [Tom] Well, you're the tailor.
- Bare hands?
- From the looks of it, yeah.
- Boy, police work
is really hard.
- So unless old Joe is
secretly pumping iron--
- You're looking for
one large, angry person.
- [Mike] Maybe I am looking
for someone like that,
but I don't think
I'll ever find him.
- [Tom] Don't touch me.
- I guess I'll need more
tape than I thought.
(rock music blaring)
- [Mike] Geez.
Maybe he should put the speakers
on the inside of his car.
- [Tom] Hey, threw meat
loaf at my mom today.
- I'm going to be involved
with a Sagittarius this week.
- Two teens overdose
on angel dust?
What?
- [Tom] What is up
with Mark Trail?
- Peter never did any dust, man.
- [Tom] He was a crack head.
- What's going on?
- Are they really dead?
I, I don't believe it's them.
There must be some mistake.
- Yeah.
yes, they're really dead.
- Where's our order?
- Man, what is so funny?
- [Mike] Did you see Russell
Baker's column this morning?
- It's great, man.
He killed them.
- What are you talking about?
- That big goon we
flattened the other night.
I guess we didn't finish
the job after all.
- Oh, my God.
- [Tom] Suddenly
the Twist and Creme
seemed a much darker place.
- Psycho might be right.
- I thought you said
no one knew it was us.
I thought you said
that no one saw us.
- Calm down.
- I'm sorry I was
thinking again.
- Just go in the car, all right?
I'll be with you in a minute.
- [Mike] Go to the car.
Bring your Dilly Bar
to the car, honey.
- [Tom] I should have
joined the PGA tour.
- [Jim] She's a
tough broad, man.
- Forget her.
What are we going to do
about our big friend?
- Or friends, man.
I say let 'em come.
- I'll throw pasta at 'em.
- I, uh, just might
scalp me a few.
- Christ, man, put
that thing away.
Someone killed Peter and Susie.
This isn't a game.
- Lay off me, man.
- I just want you to chill out.
- No way.
- Why, Jimbo?
- [Mike] I'm Generation
X, that's why.
- Because I'm
having a good time.
- [Tom] Can't you just
support me in that, Phil?
(grunting)
- He should try a
more direct approach.
- Hands off me, dirt bag!
- Come on, Mags, won't
you give me a try.
- [Mike] I'd never
touch you, Terry.
You're dirt.
- I'm 21.
- 17 is more like it, right?
- [Tom] 17 and a half.
- Look, you may be tough,
but I don't rob the cradle.
I'm old enough to be
your older sister.
- Besides, I've got a career.
- I like that.
I've always wanted to make
it with my older sister.
- Oh, so Canada
has a South, too.
- I don't want to see you.
- [Mike] Okay, Friday then?
- Yeah, well, uh,
you're not going
to do any better
in this town, baby.
- [Tom] No town is that small.
- I'm really sorry,
but my religion
forbids inter-species mating.
- [Mike] So she's,
uh, not a Unitarian?
- You're smart, aren't you?
But you'll have it,
and you will love it.
- [Mike] Heh.
No, he hasn't really
sold himself on that one.
- What are you looking at?
Eat your ice cream!
- I'm going to Dairy
Queen from now on.
- [Mike] The police
station, the hot new disco.
(knocking)
- [Tom] What's this?
- Come in.
- Doogie Howser, detective.
(hums)
- This is the report
on our double suicide.
- [Tom] And my
bibliography, too.
- The coroner fixes the
death at about 12:30 a.m.
Brain death caused by
the cervical vertebrae
being crushed.
- [Mike] I guess.
- Forensics found lots
of prints on the scene,
but few of them
are clear enough to trace.
The few fingerprints
we did get all,
uh, trace back to
members of the academy--
- [Tom] Whom I'd like to thank.
- Employees.
We've had men checking them out.
They all seem to have
pretty good alibis
as to where they
were last night.
And I checked with
mental health to see
if they had any sizable
lunatics running around,
but, uh, they didn't have any
loose nuts to fit our needs.
- [Tom] Hmm?
- Are you telling me in
your quaint way, Frank,
that we don't have any leads?
- Uh.
- Why do you hate me, sir?
- Cap, where did the
newspapers get the, uh,
drug and suicide story?
- I gave it to them.
- You gave it to them?
I don't understand.
- [Tom] I was bored.
What do you want?
- Frank, this Winster boy
ran with the bad crowd,
high school kids--
- [Tom] No!
- Running red lights,
getting drunk--
- [Tom] Wow.
- Smoking marijuana,
all the usual bad stuff.
Murder's a whole new ballgame.
Till we get a line
on this killer,
I want the press to get
nothing but misinformation.
- [Mike] So, business as usual?
- Otherwise they'll make
this guy a serial killer
or a goddamn vigilante savior.
- [Tom] Hey.
- What about the
public's right to know?
- Hey, we're concerned with
the public's right to live.
I've spoken with the parents.
They've told me they're
going to cooperate.
The last thing I want
is for this kid's gang
to go looking for revenge.
- Yeah.
Well, whatever you say, Cap.
I've got an APB out
on any one big enough
to snap a person's neck.
That ought to clear
out, uh, half the health
clubs and all the
high school teams.
- [Tom] High school teams.
(shivers)
- I think you're big enough
to handle this by yourself.
- Well, I'm going
out now and buying
something anabolic steroids.
- Frank.
- [Mike] Is that John too?
- Let's not have
any more high school
kids turn up dead, understand?
- [Mike] Hey, how about
junior high kids, is that--
- [Tom] You know, Adam worked
for scale on this film,
because he wanted to
work with this director.
(ominous music)
- [Mike] Daily meditations.
- Yo Yo Ma goes camping.
(Tom speaking gibberish)
- Pretty though.
- [Mike] Good night, folks.
- Hi.
I'll have a clown
burger and some fries.
- No.
Go home.
- [Tom] Your son's on back
order, won't be here till March.
- Don't look at him now.
His body's going
through many changes.
- [Mike] He's at that age.
- Just be patient.
We will have revenge.
- [Tom] I'll talk to the
gal in customer service.
Damn, Klingon
language camp is full.
- [Mike] God, in
voodoo, you've really
got to hand-hold your clients.
Sheez.
♪ Going 'round ♪
- Man, this place
comes alive at night.
Woo.
- [Tom] Oh, I see, she's off
to her corporate job now.
- This place is
probably great for tips.
- [Mike] Well, I'm
thinking we should expand
into chili dogs,
but I've got to seriously
consider that offer from A&W.
- [Tom] Hmm, mmm, oh,
ice cream headache.
Oh.
(gargles)
- She did one too
many Reddi-wip hits.
- [Tom] I need a
smaller tank top.
♪ Standing in the danger zone ♪
- Okay, if I diversify and
put most of my liquid assets
into 30-day CDs, I...
At any rate, my
dogs are barking.
(ominous music)
- [Mike] If he kills
her, I'll lose my faith
in zombies forever.
- Boo.
- [Tom] You know, if
he were job hunting,
his persistence would
be a good thing.
- Nice night for a walk.
- Oh, God.
It's only you.
Can't you leave me alone?
- [Tom] I just got back from
my cheap trick audition.
- No, a pretty girl like
you shouldn't be left alone.
You want a drag?
- [Mike] When they
start kissing, there's
going to be hair everywhere.
- I haven't smoked
since college.
- [Tom] I used to get lit
with Brooke Shields a lot.
- Yeah, well, I may not measure
up to those college guys
you're used to, but
they don't measure up
to mine, if you catch my drift.
- [Tom] Is he talking
about his banana seat bike?
- Listen, why don't you
just to drift off somewhere
and molest someone your own age.
- [Mike] Yeah,
that's telling him.
- I've had a long day.
- Yeah, well, that's
not all that's long.
- [Tom] Oh, again with
the phallic references.
- That's it.
I've had enough of your
childish sexual advances.
Go away!
- [Tom] Yes!
- Or I'll call the cops.
- [Tom] Knee him.
- Childish, huh?
- [Tom] Twist and Creme
internal security force.
- [Woman] No.
- [Mike] Yes.
- [Tom] Yes.
- [Woman] I told you,
he wasn't my boyfriend.
I didn't even like him.
- Then why did you come
into the alley with him?
- [Mike] Oh, right,
blame the victim.
- I didn't go anywhere with him.
He was trying to rape me.
He had a knife.
- All right, all right.
I'm sorry, miss.
Calm down.
- Geez, you victims
are so touchy.
- And he would have if
it wasn't for the giant.
(sniffles)
- [Tom] Can I get back in
on the son of the governor, JJ?
- I was knocked out.
But when, but when I came to--
- Big scene.
- [Mike] Yeah.
- This--
- [Mike] Acting.
- This giant--
- [Mike] Emotional memory.
Wow.
- [Man] Giant?
- [Mike] Like LT?
- He--
- [Mike] Sims?
- He was--
- [Mike] Babaro?
- His eyes, his eyes
were like white.
- Say, uh, sorry to
bug you, but could I
get a cone with sprinkles
and, oh, bad time.
Sorry.
- Don't you believe me?
- No, no.
I believe that's what you saw.
(laughs)
Chet, I'm finished with her.
Get her out of here.
(laughs)
This man will care of you, miss.
- His eyes.
- [Tom] It's Captain
Sensitive on the job here.
- His eyes were like white.
- Hey, Frank.
- Oh, no, this guy.
- [Mike] No.
- What have we got here?
(imitates_voice)
- Well, she claims
he tried to rape her.
That checks out with what
the owner of this place
tells me about our boy Jim here.
He used to come around with
his gang and bother the girls.
- Yeah.
Did that frail young
thing impale Jimmy boy
with a baseball bat?
- She claims it was
the Jolly Green Giant.
- [Tom] Frankly, I
think it was Sprout.
- You believe her?
- Hell no.
These kids are so
whacked out on drugs,
they don't know what they see.
- Well, doc, this
is one kid you're
going to have trouble
convincing that this
was a drug-induced
hallucination.
- [Tom] You're going to protect
the Twist and Creme Corporation,
aren't you son?
- Jim Barton.
I've known his
family all my life.
(imitating voice)
- Sorry, doc.
- For what?
The kid was a bum, he was
a disgrace to his family.
- [Mike] Yah, he goes
up with his sentences.
- Maybe he nailed
himself with a baseball,
you know what I mean.
- Yeah, I got it
drug-induced suicide.
- Hey, Frank, I believe
you're coming along.
- Thanks, doc.
- [Tom] So, should they just
leave him there, or not?
(ominous music)
- Why, it's a perfectly
good Peanut Buster Parfait.
- [Tom] Mmm.
- [Mike] Well, I wonder if this
knife's related to the case.
Nah, couldn't be.
- [Tom] I have no
idea what I'm doing.
When I get out of
my teens, I'm going
to be a great investigator.
(upbeat rock music)
(phone ringing)
♪ Slow ride ♪
♪ Stroke me, stroke me ♪
- Mod hair Ken bulks up.
(phone ringing)
- [Woman] Bobby, your
phone is ringing.
- Yeah, I can hear it, Ma.
(phone ringing)
- [Mike] Guy's got a real
Scott Thorson quality.
- [Woman] Get it, Bobby.
You've been in there a while.
- [Tom] Oh, it's probably
my chest grease supplier.
- Hello.
- Bob, this is Ames.
I just heard it on the radio,
What are we going to go?
- [Tom] U2 tickets are on sale.
- [Bobby] Amy, calm down.
What's wrong?
- What's wrong?
Jim's dead, Bob.
Didn't you hear it on the radio?
They found his body
behind drive-in.
He's dead.
- Okay, baby, just
try and relax.
- Relax?
Don't you understand?
We're next.
He's killed Peter
and Susie and Jim.
We're next.
- Do you think
you could go next?
- It's Amy, Ma.
- [Woman] Oh, well,
say hello for me, dear.
- [Bobby] My mother says hello.
- Are you crazy?
Don't you see that we're next?
- All right.
Where are you?
- [Tom] I'm, I'm here, I think.
- I'm at home.
- [Bobby] Is there anyone there?
- No.
- Uh, except for me.
- I'm alone.
My mother went to--
- Good.
Now listen.
Stay where you are,
I'm coming right over.
- [Mike] Small comfort, I know.
- Lock the doors and
don't let anyone in, okay?
- Okay.
- I'll be right there.
- But don't let me in.
- Don't worry.
Nothing's going to happen.
- [Mike] How did this get here?
- Whoa, check out the teddy.
- [Tom] We've taken the Sears
Auto Center waiting room
and turned it into headquarters.
- [Mike] Whoa, Stiff
Bater is pissed.
- Hey, you smashed my sandwich!
(grunting)
- [Tom] Does anybody
have their gun?
- Anybody got
handcuffs or anything?
(screaming)
Please, sir, just
pay the parking fine.
- [Tom] Boy, wait till
my Young Life meeting
hears about this.
- Take a good look, friend.
There's your killer.
- [Mike] Mine, sir?
You mean it?
(screaming)
- This scene was cut
from the program.
- [Mike] Tear gas, mace, anyone?
- James Earl Powell.
We picked him up in New Castle.
- He was bringing coals.
- He was trying to rob
a check cashing store.
James is a very bad boy.
He was on probation.
- Let me guess, assault.
- [Tom] No, a pepper.
Ha ha.
- Yeah, right.
Seems he likes to beat
up people and rob 'em.
You may have noticed.
- I'm Adam West.
- [Man] James is a
terrifyingly strong dude.
- [Tom] Dude, sir?
- Then why did he kill the kids?
Then why did he kill the kids?
You know none of
them were robbed.
- [Tom] Take two.
- I don't know, maybe he
was working for somebody,
maybe he's got a new hobby.
But we've got him now
and we'll find out
just as soon as he talks.
- [Mike] Now, Chief O'Hara, oh.
- What's the matter, Frank?
A little flesh wound
because you couldn't
solve this case yourself?
- I'll check the script.
- Look, the object is
to clear these cases
as soon as possible.
- Maybe too soon.
- You're trying to say
we got the wrong man?
- Look, I just don't think that
Mr. James there is our man.
- Do you have
somebody else in mind?
- [Tom] Well, my uncle's nice.
- It's just a
feeling, that's all.
- I just feel like crying.
- Oh, yes.
Feeling.
Must be that
policeman's intuition
you've developed after all
these years with the force.
Oh, come on, Frank.
You're just a little
ticked because you couldn't
grab the brass ring and
solve this case yourself.
Come on, you've got a
lot of years ahead of you
to blow cases.
Just be happy this one's solved.
- [Mike] Yeah, come on.
Where's that's smile?
- Come on, Frank.
- [Tom] No, not the belt!
- [Mike] No!
- I'll buy you a drink.
- It is 10 a.m.
- [Mike] Guy just got a timeout.
(upbeat synth music)
(grunting)
- [Tom] The word
truncheon springs to mind.
Cudgel.
- Bad boy.
- [Mike] Oh.
- Oh, that was easy for him.
He just pretended
it was Tim Burton.
- [Mike] Uh, that
didn't help much, sir.
Thanks anyway.
- [Tom] Auditions
for the band Fear.
- The three faces of Steve.
(screaming)
- Did you have to order
me a corn-god, sir.
- [Tom] Adam West did his
own stunts in this scene.
- [Mike] Could I get a
booster chair for my friend.
- Just need to be
treated with respect.
Could I get another
Shirley Temple, please.
- Well, here's to the
ones who got away.
- [Tom] Away, heh.
- Hope my pirate
meal has onion rings.
Take me away 7-Up.
- [Tom] This is
all too familiar.
- How long's it been, Frank?
- I don't know.
- You know me too well.
- Two years.
- Oh, you'll get over it.
Took me about two
centuries, but it'll work.
Hey.
Come on, this is a celebration.
The cases is closed.
- [Mike] Well, if
it's a celebration,
why are we at Chi Chi's?
- I know, I'm sorry.
- I can't do this before
breakfast, I'm not like you.
- You should have seen it.
I mean, this kid was
impaled with a baseball bat.
I just don't understand how
this guy James Earl could do it?
- Maybe James Earl has
a great batting average.
- [Tom] But it's the RBI's
that count, isn't it?
- Cap, this wasn't
like anything.
I mean, look at this kid.
He's got a baseball bat shoved
right through his stomach.
- Frank, I did not come here
to look at dirty pictures.
You take enough of
stuff home with you,
pretty soon there's not going
to be anything else at home.
- [Mike] And you got to
leave room for liquor.
- Hey!
- What?
- This is a celebration.
Hey!
Hey, the case is closed.
- [Tom] Long live the case!
- [Man] Hey!
- [Tom] Hey!
- [Mike] Hey!
- Hey!
- [Tom] Hey!
- [Mike] Hey!
- Hey
- [Tom] Hey!
- [Mike] Hey!
- Hey!
- [Tom] Hey!
Hey!
- Hey!
- [Mike] Hey!
- It's her first
zombie commissioned
in a couple of years, so
she's babysitting the case.
(roars)
- [Mike] Your mystery date.
- [Tom] It's five a.m.
and Mr. Zombie's day
is just beginning.
- [Mike] He's off for a
long day of job interviews.
- Uh, I've got to get a new bad.
Slept like crap again.
- [Tom] No, no, don't help me.
I've got it.
- [Mike] Watch my
casket, will you.
Don't drive it.
- Wow, he's really
last his looks.
- [Tom] Just once I'd
like to see a zombie
with a little more
get up and go.
- Eh.
(humming)
- [Tom] Don't.
- [Mike] Sorry.
- It went from a high rise
exterior to someone's basement.
- [Tom] Oh, he's hitting
the note pretty hard there.
- [Mike] If I had a girlfriend,
she'd be sitting right
there, right now.
- He needs to unify
his design concept.
- [Mike] Corduroy
chair's nice, though.
- [Tom] Mmm, self-bondage
really doesn't work out.
- [Frank] This
case isn't closed.
- [Mike] I just realized
something we're not
going to bother
showing the audience.
Ha!
(light synth music)
He's being stalked
by Depeche Mode.
(hums)
- [Tom] Johnson's
wedding got out of hand.
- [Mike] Remind me
never to frost my hair.
(hums)
- Wait a minute.
What's Charlie Watts
doing in there?
- [Tom] I'll order a couple
of these in wallet size.
- [Mike] Oh, Phil
looked nice in this one.
- Oh, man, that Barbra
Streisand concert was great.
- [Tom] Geez, I look
so much older on film.
♪ My own personal Jesus ♪
Hey, Frank, your head cheese
sandwich is getting warm.
- Wait a minute.
- [Tom] Anne Jillian's
not a real blonde!
(laughing)
- Thank God.
I thought I was going crazy.
- [Mike] I may need
another glass of milk.
- Frank, are you crazy?
Those goddamn pictures again.
Is this why you dragged me
out of bed this time of night?
I've got to be back in here
at six o'clock in the morning.
- Cap, Cap, look.
Just hear me out.
All I want is
permission to pick up
this woman for questioning.
Her name's, uh, Molly--
- [Mike] The hoople.
- [Man] Hey, don't be so upset.
Hey.
Hey, you going to come
into my neighborhood,
you've got to pay the toll.
- [Tom] He's flashing
back without us.
- [Mike] Adam, psst, we
need video support here.
- Molly Mokembe.
- You know this woman, Cap?
- Know her?
- [Mike] We did improv together.
- Oh, sure, she's,
uh, some kind of, uh,
voodoo palm reader in the
black section of town.
- [Mike] I'm Batman.
- I ran into her a
couple of times, uh,
but she has nothing
to do with this case.
- I don't know, Cap.
I mean, this woman was at
the scene of both murders,
and they took place miles apart.
- Who knows, maybe
the batty old broad
likes to follow
ambulances around.
- [Tom] Yes, I said batty.
- Besides, we have our
murderer, Frank, remember?
- You know, if you, if you
give this kind of stuff
to the press, they're going
to have a field day with you.
She's a harmless old
coconut, believe me.
- [Tom] As a coconut,
sir, I'm offended.
- I just wanted to be
thorough, that's all.
- You are thorough, Frank.
- [Tom] You're gentle.
- But you don't look too good.
Why don't you, uh, go home
and take a little rest.
- [Tom] Quit the
force, move away.
- I'm sorry.
- [Tom] Sorry?
Let's talk Batman, huh.
- Don't be sorry, Frank.
Just go get some rest.
That's an order.
- And order me this.
- Goodnight, Captain.
- [Tom] Nightcap?
Did you say nightcap?
Oh, don't mind if I do.
(ominous music)
- [Tom] It's flushing his head.
- Oh, let me get this straight.
Let's make a Batman movie
but not call Adam West.
- [Tom] Look at me, I could
have worked with Nicholson.
- [Mike] I'll call Burt Ward.
I know he's not busy.
- No one can milk a
shot like Adam West.
- [Mike] He had more
expressions when wore a mask.
- Hello?
What, 900-SPANK-ME?
I can't.
I must stop.
- [Tom] Wow.
(phone ringing)
- Hey, Steven, Robby's upstairs.
He's tied Chip to the
bed with Doddy's nylons.
(phone ringing)
- [Man] I'm coming, I'm coming.
- [Fred] Team dad.
- Yeah, what is it?
- Fred, it's me.
How's Mary taking it?
- [Fred] Well, Tom,
you know women.
- [Tom] Who's Mary?
- [Mike] He's married.
- [Tom] Who's Fred?
- [Crow] I'm confused.
- [Mike] Who's that guy?
It's Ted McGinley.
- I, uh, here you
have a suspect.
- What we have here is trouble.
(doors clanking)
- I don't care.
I feel like an idiot,
and I'm binding
- Oh, come on, Tom.
Get into it.
I mean, that Batman play
seemed important to Crow,
and he made these
costumes, and--
- Whoa.
What the heck is--
- Crow!
Where's your costume?
We're supposed to be
doing your Batman play?
- Batman play,
(laughs)
I thought You knew.
I dropped that stink
bomb a long time ago.
- What?
Oh, you rotten son of a--
- Yeah, yeah, that decision
goes back a couple of weeks.
Funny I didn't say
anything about it to you.
Well, what are you going to do?
- Well, we're
standing here looking
like a couple of ninnies.
- Yeah.
- Well, yeah, you are.
(laughs)
Well, wow, what the heck!
We can still do it.
C'mon.
It's the--
(sings)
(laughs)
Riddle me this, Batman.
- Crow!
- Geez.
It's a play, come on.
You know, these costumes
turned out pretty good.
How's that feel in the
crotch there, Mike?
- Would you get out of there!
- Oh!
Sure, I go the extra mile,
this is the thanks I get.
I'm going to go
work on my script.
- For crying out loud.
- Mike.
Mike.
Something's happening.
I like my costume.
- No you don't.
- Yes, I do.
It gives me special bat powers.
- God, we've got to cut
you out of that thing.
Let's--
- Hang in there, old chum.
Alfred, don't touch me.
I'm Batman.
Aunt Harriet.
I need cookies, cookies.
(upbeat synth music)
- Molly Makembe's
mixed up in this--
- [Mike] Stupid Batman.
- I want you to get the
hell out of there now
and get down here
to the station.
We're going to find this witch--
- [Mike] Wake up.
- I'm out the door.
- [Tom] Okay, super.
Ba-bye.
- God, I miss my tights.
(dramatic orchestral music)
- [Mike] Just a little
snapshot of Adam
and the young
Philadelphians here.
- [Tom] This is Tim Burton's
last night on earth.
- What is he going to do,
staple himself to death?
Oh, it's a gun.
- [Mike] When I said
I'm out the door,
it was really just
an expression.
Okay, now I am out of the door.
- [Tom] The Orlon sweater's
got to get hot, huh?
(roars)
- Nice kitty.
(gun firing)
- [Mike] Watch tower!
- [Tom] Well, sorry about that.
I'm in kind of a hurry.
- [Mike] Sir, if
you'll just take a look
at the literature, I can,
I can come back and
we can discuss what--
(roars)
- [Tom] Jack
Palance fights back.
- I'll just hop in here.
Certainly don't need
to close the door.
He he.
(roars)
- [Mike] You going right home?
Because if you're going
home, I can get a ride
with you, but if you're going--
- [Tom] Look, I'm sorry.
It's, it isn't
convenient to carpool.
You live in the cemetery,
I live downtown.
- I really could have
planned this better.
(growls)
- [Mike] See, this
wouldn't have happened
if he'd been
wearing a seat belt.
- Well, no need to linger, heh.
(singing)
- Steve, I followed you to work.
You don't really work
for a missile plant.
Steve, put the gone down.
Steve!
(imitating gunfire)
Bob was right.
- [Mike] There.
- What the hell
took you so long?
- I was trying to get
my mom's cash card so
we could get the
hell out of town.
- Oh, Bob, you're
not kidding, are you?
- Amy, I think you're right,
someone is trying to kill us.
Because Jim tried to make a
speed bump out of that clown.
And I do not want to die.
- [Mike] Shut up.
- Well, where are we going?
When are we leaving?
- [Mike] Shut up.
- Well, we could go right
now, but I don't we're
going to get very
far on 20 bucks.
- What about your
mom's cash card?
- Like I said, I
tried to get my--
- [Mike] Shut up.
- Mom's cash card.
I couldn't.
- [Tom] Shut up, you.
- Don't you have
cash around here?
- [Mike] Shut up.
- Take a look around.
I hardly even see my parents.
- [Mike] Shut up.
- Great, we're stuck.
- [Tom] Shut up.
- [Mike] Shut up.
- No way.
- [Tom] You shut up.
- Jim was telling me that we
should knock over his uncle's
garage if ever we needed money.
- [Mike] Shut up.
- And we need money now.
- His uncle's garage?
- Yeah, Jim always
had it figured out,
said he was saving
it for an emergency.
- Well, this is an emergency.
- [Mike] Shut up.
- Let's do it.
- [Tom] But should I
get into my underwear?
- [Mike] Oh, the
zombie drives a K-car.
Hmm, sensible.
(birds chirping)
- This is Charlie 117, come in.
- [Tom] I've got birds, over.
- Oh, I knew it.
- [Tom] Shut up.
- I'll be right there.
- Water in the basement.
Darn it!
- [Mike] Your worst nightmare,
a cop with a learner's permit.
- [Tom] Hal Needham was brought
in to direct this scene.
(siren wailing)
And that's all.
- Oh, that's fine, we'll just
walk to the curb from here.
- [Man] You two, get
those people out of here.
- Oh, yeah, you can use it.
- Hi, Frank.
We've got another one
just like the last three.
- Neck broken?
- Yeah, like a twig.
- [Mike] Oh, nice image.
- How old is the kid?
- I'd say about 43.
- What, an old man?
- Yeah.
- Hey, thanks, Frank.
We can't all look
as young as you now.
- [Tom] Oh, great, he's back.
- Do you, uh, do
you think this could
have been done by the same
assailant as the others.
- I'd stake my semi-professional
reputation on it.
(laughs)
- [Tom] Stop.
- So, who is this guy?
- That's the kicker, he's
the last kid's father.
- [Tom] Father.
- Oh, I left my lights on again.
- [Man] Hey, Frank!
Don't you want to
check the house?
- I'm more interested
in the crowd.
- [Mike] I'm, uh, running
for state auditor.
Hi, folks!
Hi.
- Come on, Amy.
We'll buy you clothes when--
- [Tom] Oh, look, she
put her breasts on.
- Should I leave
a note for my mom?
- Ah, she'll just
think you got lost in--
- But should I bring my sports
bra in case I get chased?
- [Mike] This spot
reserved for Viper.
- [Tom] Guests being
stalked by zombies
stay at Best Western Hotel.
- See, no prob.
Mr. Key was right where
old Jim said it would be.
- [Tom] He's dressed for
ladies' night at Shenanigans.
- Yeah, well, we're not
going to end up like,
Jim, you hear me?
Let's just get this cash,
and then we're history.
- [Tom] Hey.
If Mr. Blackstone
was a zombie, he'd
kill her just for that skirt.
- Mmhmm.
- This is a big garage.
- [Mike] See, she's
not that dumb.
- Yeah, a little too big.
- I wonder where they
keep their money.
- Yeah, good question,
a little too good.
- [Tom] Oh, must you
superlative everything?
- [Mike] It's a little
ominous in here.
A little too ominous.
- A lot of cars in here.
- [Mike] A little too
a lot of cars in here.
- [Tom] Would you please.
A Francis Ford Coppola
production or a Kenneth Branagh
film Kera Cutley in Ali
Sheedy's "Frankenstein."
- [Mike] Tommy Lee Jones.
(roars)
- He's a great actor.
- [Mike] Yeah.
- We ain't ever going
to find this money
if we don't split up.
- [Tom] Are you
breaking up with me?
- I'm going to go
check over here.
You go check over there.
Just check around, okay?
- This place is creepy.
I don't want to go
there by myself.
- Just do as I told you, okay?
- [Tom] Check out
that dark corner.
- Go.
Go in.
♪ You spin me
right round, baby ♪
♪ Right round like
a record, baby ♪
Remember that song?
- [Tom] No.
I thought she was being
followed by Al Gore.
- Why's he crab-walking?
- [Mike] Hey, is
my Buick ready yet?
- [Tom] Hello!
Is there a salesman
who can help me?
(growls)
- Boy, the zombie's got to clear
that frog out of his throat.
(coughs)
- [Mike] He sounds
like Harvey Fierstein.
- [Tom] Oh, he's balding, look.
- Oh, so does that
mean his grandfather
on his mother's side
was a balding zombie?
- [Mike] Where are those
commemorative place mats?
Stupid garage.
- [Tom] That's clearly
not the original actor.
- [Mike] Hi.
What can I do you for?
- [Tom] Wow!
(upbeat synth music)
- [Mike] Howdy.
That your zombie, ma'am?
- [Tom] Stop that.
Let me move my bike.
Hang on.
- [Mike] That's a really
trivial use of her dark powers.
(screams)
- [Tom] Cut, cut.
Tia, you're supposed to be in
your underwear in this scene.
(screams)
- No!
♪ Start spreading news ♪
(screams)
- [Mike] Well, Tia,
it's still better
than working with Mike Myers.
(growls)
- [Tom] Excuse me, miss.
That's for authorized
personnel only.
- [Mike] This is a big garage.
- Yeah, it's even
got a subway stop.
(growls)
♪ Some enchanted evening ♪
- [Mike] How'd he do that?
- [Tom] He's a pro.
- [Mike] She's hiding
behind a window!
- [Tom] Oh.
Oh, that one's got a
way with zombies, huh?
- [Mike] Mm-hmm.
(grunting)
- Oh!
Right on his luggage rack!
- [Mike] Admittedly, that's
an aggressive sales technique,
but, you know.
- [Tom] You're right,
paint job looks fine.
Sorry I complained.
Ba-bye.
- That was great.
I've never been handled
like that before.
- [Mike] This is a
really big garage.
- [Tom] Shari
Belafonte in "Harper."
- Well, looky here.
- How you diddly doing?
- Aren't you in the wrong
neighborhood little girl?
- [Mike] I'm Batman.
- Looks like I missed
the start of the party.
Why don't you show me
where the guests are going.
Get in the car, witch.
- Yes, Mr. Churchman.
- [Tom] Oh, is your
Batmobile in the shop?
- [Mike] Shut up.
(ominous synth music)
♪ Her name is Rio and she-- ♪
- [Mike] No.
No, never.
Look, it's Dondi the zombie.
- The zombie is deep in
the rough on the 13th.
He's got to put this
shot up to par the hole.
- [Mike] The hell is my grave?
Last time I crawled into the
wrong one, it was a mess.
- [Tom] You know,
ironically, they end up
busting the Zombie
for task evasion.
- Hey, uh, can I
have my thorax back?
- [Mike] Mr. Zombie,
I, I just need you
to sign this deposition.
It'll just take a sec.
♪ What would you sing
if I sang out of tune ♪
♪ Instead of what I mean ♪
He's choking up.
- Boy, I'm dead on my feet.
He he.
Dead, oh well.
- [Mike] It's doing
the nasty plunge.
Thud.
- [Tom] I mean, what's he, ew,
he's giving himself
a tongue bath.
Ew!
- Don't be afraid, Frank.
He won't bite you.
- [Mike] He might snap your
neck, but he won't bite you.
- Cap?
- [Mike] Aren't you Adam West
from "Lady
Chatterley's Lover 2"?
- The voodoo woman explained it
to me on the way over, Frank.
She made this kid a zombie
so it would avenge itself
against its murderers,
and avenge her against me.
- Oh!
- Against you?
- It's a long, sad
old story, Frank--
- [Tom] Yeah, I'll say.
- From before I
was on the force.
- [Tom] I had this
great cave, you see.
- A really sad story.
- He killed this boy's father
for trying to save my life.
- Is that true?
- That's true, Frank.
- Oh.
- But you see, zombies
lose their energy
after they revenge themselves.
So there'll be nobody around
to revenge old Molly Makembe.
- Oops.
- This case is closed, Frank.
(gun firing)
- [Tom] Oh!
Oh, wow.
Probably should have
seen that coming.
(growls)
- Oh, ah, there's one
spot I just can't do.
- This is the last evil you
will do on earth, Mr. Churchman.
- I think she's
going for some sort
of Elvis Patois kind of thing.
(growls)
- [Mike] I've seen
some raunchy stuff,
but that's disgusting.
(chants)
- [Mike] Should have never had
those little Vietnamese peppers.
- The man is a pig.
(growls)
- [Tom] Eh, it's just
a cry for attention.
- [Mike] Rick Baker,
you've done it again.
(gun firing)
- [Tom] You shot
me, you son of a--
- The paperwork's really
mounting here, sir.
(laughs)
- [Tom] Case closed.
How about a drink?
- [Frank] What are you
gonna do now, Captain?
You gonna kill me, too?
- I've got no choice, Frank.
- [Mike] Well, that backfired.
- [Man] Come on, Frank,
take it like a man.
(growls)
- [Mike] What the.
(gun firing)
This isn't a very
effective cemetery.
(gun firing)
- [Tom] They need heavier dirt.
- [Tom] Ah-ma, I'm-a, hum-a.
- [Mike] Ms. Jane Pittman!
- [Tom] Hum-a, hum-a.
- You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything--
(chokes)
- Frank!
Help, Frank, help!
Frank!
Help me, Frank.
- [Tom] Help, Spock.
Help me!
- Frank!
- He just wants to play, sir.
- Kill, kill me, Frank!
Frank!
(screams)
- Wow.
So hell's right there.
- [Tom] Yeah, that's why you
should call before you dig.
- [Mike] Are you mad, sir?
(dramatic synth music)
- [Tom] You were the
bestest Batman ever.
Good bye, Cesar Romero.
- Wow, the Lutheran
church ladies will
be so surprised in the morning.
- [Mike] Well, take a
spin by Grandpa's grave
while I'm here.
- [Tom] Hey, don't
step on my grave!
- Hey, that hurts!
- [Mike] Hey, watch
it, you loser!
- Ow, my chest!
- [Tom] Standing
right on my toes!
- [Mike] Stepped on your mother.
- Get that clown out of here.
- [Tom] And turn out
the light on your way.
(upbeat rock music)
- Graveyard scene.
(imitating vocals)
- [Mike] Look at that, they
put the garbage incinerator
right next to the cemetery.
(impersonates singer)
- [Mike] Is this
song in Esperanto?
(singing gibberish)
- [Mike] Read the Bantam book.
Buy the drink glass.
The Washington family honors.
- [Tom] You know, Tia Carrere
went on to a Hollywood career,
but I was sure that
Hamish McEwen would
be the breakout
star of this one.
- [Mike] Which one
is Jon Mikl Thor?
- [Tom] He was the
one with the badge.
There were two
Biddles in this film.
- Yeah, and both Biddles were
in the Yiddish
theater production
of "Yiddle with a Fiddle."
- [Tom] With Biddles.
- [Mike] Hey,
look, Dean Hagopian
played the crusty and
cynical medical examiner.
"You are looking for one
large angry individual."
- [Tom] Mike, if you talk
in that voice one more time,
I'm going to have to kill you.
- [Mike] Okay, I won't.
I'll stake my semi-professional
reputation on it.
- [Tom] Kill him.
- You kill him.
- [Tom] Soundtrack available
in cut out bins everywhere.
- [Mike] $0.85 for
the soundtrack.
- [Tom] That's right,
some of your favorites.
- You know, they are
using the term artists
here very loosely.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
- [Mike] Look, Virgin Steele.
I went to school
with a Virgil Steele.
- [Tom] That's so
interesting, Michael.
- [Mike] You know, I'm
really disappointed that Abba
weren't in the soundtrack.
- [Tom] Really?
- [Mike] Oh, actually no,
I was just killing time.
- [Mike] I like Chess, though.
- [Tom] Thank you.
Hey, you know, Jon Mikl
Thor was in the movie,
he wrote the music,
his band Thor
was featured on the
soundtrack, incidental music
was by Thorchestra.
He just did everything
in this film.
He's like, just like
a Michael Landon.
- Oh, so you mean
he's bad-wetter?
- [Tom] No, no, I don't
mean he's a bed wetter.
- [Crow] Well, then what
are you trying to get at?
- [Tom] The concept that
I'm trying to apply--
- [Crow] He's the
long-distance runner.
(doors clanking)
- Okay, how we doing?
You know, you guys, I think
that Adam West will really
appreciate these letters,
on account of the fact
that we gave him
quite a lot of ribbing
during the film and all.
So, um, well, who's ready?
- Oh!
Oh, me!
Me, I'm done.
I'll go first.
I'm ready.
Me, me!
- Crow.
- Oh.
Oh, okay.
"Dear Mr. West, I very
much enjoyed that thing
"that you did that was good.
"It's kind of fun when
I see you in stuff.
"Do you feel pretty crappy
now that "Danger Theater"
"and "Last Precinct"
has been canceled?"
- I bet he does.
- "I'm sending you
all my allowance.
"Please don't buy beer with it.
"Ha ha.
"Yours truly, Crow T. Robot."
- Neat.
- Well, that was, that
was very good, Crow.
There are certain
parts that I would
change if I were, if I
were writing the letter.
- Well, it's the
Bible, but, you know.
- Okay, well, whatever.
Uh, Tom.
You had something.
- Okay, here we.
(clears throat)
"Dear Adam.
"I'm sorry to hear about the
accident at the sportsman show.
"Oh, just saw
"Zombie Nightmare."
"You look good in a mustache.
"Real nice work in
that scene where
"the zombie pulls
you underground.
"Oh, and, hey, I heard that
"Lady Chatterley's Lover 2"
"is okay,
"although I'm not
allowed to see it.
"Well, I'm running out of room.
"We'll talk soon.
"Tom Servo."
- That's, uh, very good, Tom.
- Thank you.
- Again, there are
things, you know,
maybe we could just go in
there, Strunk and White
kind of a thing.
Ah, Gypsy, you have
something, don't you?
Let me just, you want to, uh--
- Yes.
- Okay.
- I wrote a poem for Mr. West.
Go ahead.
(clears_throat)
Just whenever you're--
- "I used to like you when you
"were a Caped Crusader way more
"than even Darth Vader.
"Back then you were the best,
"but now you are
like all the rest.
"That's all, so see you later."
- Oh, very nice.
- That's very good.
- Very good.
- Does anyone have anything
else for, uh, Adam West?
- Uh.
- How about you guys, do
you anything for Adam West?
(moans)
- Geez, they don't
really tell you
how to reverse these things.
Oh, hi!
Having a few technical
difficulties.
Look, Clay, I'm sorry, I
didn't mean to make you undead.
I was just fooling around.
It happens.
Maybe this magic powder
will reverse the spell.
Shazam!
Babalu!
(speaking foreign language)
Qvc!
You put that down!
You put that down.
Put that down.
Put it down.
Down.
Bad zombie!
Bad.
Now push the button.
Be a good zombie.
Push the, you push the button!
Push it.
You push the button!
Say, this zombie
stuff is kind of nice.
Heh.
(light synth music)
(speaking foreign language)
(roars)